I do auto hail repair, hail storms, image on cars.
I do 5.5 million, I want to be at 15 million next year.
If I'm hiring basically a leadership, you know, C-suite, bench, COO,
what have you seen as the most effective way to design compensation
and decision-making structure for a team like this
so that performance scales without eroding owner control or margins?
If you were doing private expansion, which you are, you own all the shops,
I had yet to see someone do like an exceptional job expanding without having
the equivalent of an operator boots on the ground in each store
that has no tie to the bottom line.
Right at the level that you're hiring for is kind of the transition between
what you run ads and when you start doing targeted outreach
for the level of person that you're looking for.
You'll probably want to reach out to 500 or so.
And if you're struggling with your local area, you can offer every location package
because oftentimes you'll have people who are, they'll trick,
they'll trick us entrepreneurs.
And they'll be like, it's on the processes and systems.
And it's like, those people hate talking to people.
And that's not what you need relief from right now.
You need probably more people to handle shit.
But a really good operator can just come into just about any business about it
because they're usually two levels above, like they're not fixing cars.
They're fixing people.
And that's the same.
Sure.
Right. And so I have a hard time saying like,
this is the hard and fast way that you should do this.
It's going to depend on the talent.
Having a small tie to the overall profitability of the business is not a bad idea.
Then as the business grows, that 10 or 20%, that percentage stays the same, but the pie increases.